flyingmule.com 2019-08-12

# The Flying Mule: Privacy Policy

###### Privacy Policy

This policy covers 1) The Flying Mule's treatment of personal information we collect when you visit our site and use our services; and 2) treatment of personal information that our partners and affiliates collect from you. This policy is not applicable to the practices of companies that The Flying Mule does not control or own, or the practices of people that The Flying Mule does not employ or manage. 

###### Information Collection and Use

The Flying Mule collects personal information when you purchase or products, register for one of our services, and when you enter contests or promotions. We may also receive personal information from our partners, affiliates, and advertisers. The Flying Mule asks for your name, email address, mailing address and phone number. Once you have supplied us with this information, you are no longer anonymous. 

From time to time, The Flying Mule may use the information you provide us to send you newsletters, updates about our services, and special offers on products. You may opt out of these lists at the time you register or make a purchase, or you may opt out afterwards by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email contacts, or by sending email to “[unsubscribe@flyingmule.com](mailto:unsubscribe@flyingmule.com).”

The Flying Mule also automatically receives information from your browser, and records this information on our server logs. This information may include your IP address, The Flying Mule cookie information and the page(s) you requested during your visit. This information is currently used only to supply you with personalized access to our services, and to make statistical recordings of generic site access information.

###### Information Sharing and Disclosure

The Flying Mule will never sell or rent your personal information to anyone without your permission. We will only share this information about you with other companies when we have your express consent to do so, or when we need to do so in order to provide you with a product or service at your request. Any company that receives your information from us, unless we have expressly informed you otherwise, does not have the right to use your information beyond what is necessary to assist us with your request. We may also provide your information if it is subpoenaed or required by a court order or legal process. 

###### Cookies

The Flying Mule may set and read cookies on your computer. We may also allow our affiliates and partners to set and read cookies on your computer. The use of cookies by other companies through The Flying Mule is subject to their own privacy policies and this privacy policy should not be taken as applicable to any company except The Flying Mule. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to cookies set by The Flying Mule. The cookies we currently use on our system are only there to provide you with login access to our specialized services. 

###### Deleting your information

You may request deletion of your information by sending an email to [support@flyingmule.com](mailto:support@flyingmule.com). 

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Flying Mule may amend this policy at any time. If we make significant changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting an announcement in a prominent place on our site. 

###### Questions, Comments and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions please contact us.
